W. R. "Bob" Poage U.S. Government papers, Inclusive: 1912-1981, undated, Bulk: 1960-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Departments, 1916-1981, undated; 2
  - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1964-1979, undated; 6
    - Printed Materials, 1967-1970 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Printed Materials, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Printed Materials, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Printed Materials, 1977-1979 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Program Guide to Model Neighborhoods in Demonstration Cities, “Improving the Quality of Urban Life”, 1967 December (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Reports and Resolutions, 1965-1966 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Urban Renewal, Waco, Clippings, 1971 March (Box 149 OVZ, Folder 2)
  - Department of Interior, 1948-1979, undated; 7
    Subseries VII contains materials relating to the Department of the Interior. Documents from the Bureau of Reclamation, Fish and Wildlife Service, Geological Survey, and National Park Service feature prominently in the subseries. Topics such as national parks (including Big Bend National Park), federal land management, wildlife refuges, and water supply are addressed at length.
    Folders in this subseries are organized alphabetically by agency or material type. Overall, the materials are in good condition.
    - Announcements, 1968-1972 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Announcements, 1973-1978 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Arctic Gas Project, Correspondence and Report, 1975 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Big Bend National Park, Information Packet, 1971-1972 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Big Bend National Park, Master Plan, 1971 October (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Big Bend National Park, Master Plan, 1972 January 15 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Big Bend National Park, Statement of West Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1972 January 15 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Big Thicket Association (BTA), Handbook for Members, 1970 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA), Correspondence, 1972 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of Indian Affairs (BIA), Report, “American Indians and Their Federal Relationship”, 1972 March (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Bureau of Land Management (BLM), Pamphlet, “Can I Really Get Free or Cheap Public Land?”, 1978 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Bureau of Outdoor Recreation (BOR), Report, 1971 April-May (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Bureau of Reclamation, Information Packet, 1962 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of Reclamation, Information Packet, 1967 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Bureau of Reclamation, Press Releases, 1979 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Reclamation, “Transmission Study 190”, 1968 February (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Sport Fisheries and Wildlife, Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Coal, Fact Sheet, 1974 November (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1953 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), Correspondence, 1952-1963 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), Correspondence, 1972-1978, undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), “Endangered Species Technical Bulletin”, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), Fishery Leaflets, 1948-1949 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), National Wildlife Refuges, Leaflets (1 of 2), 1954-1966 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), National Wildlife Refuges, Leaflets (2 of 2), 1954-1966 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Fish and Wildlife Service (FWS), “Report of Investigations of the Eagle Problem in Southwest Texas and New Mexico”, 1963 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Geological Survey, Brochure, “The United States Geological Survey”, circa 1974 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Geological Survey, Brochure, “Tools for Planning”, 1971 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Geological Survey, Brochure, “Topographic Maps”, circa 1960s (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Geological Survey, “Geologic and Water-Supply Reports and Maps, Texas”, 1968 January (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Geological Survey, “Geologic and Water-Supply Reports and Maps, Texas”, 1973 January (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Geological Survey, “Index to Topographic Mapping in Texas”, 1959 November (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Geological Survey, “Index to Topographic Mapping in Texas”, 1967 November (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Geological Survey, “Index to Topographic Mapping in Texas”, 1973 April (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Geological Survey, Maps, Ground Water in the Ogallala Formation, 1969 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Geological Survey, National Topographic Mapping Program, State Summary, Texas, 1960 February (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Geological Survey, Press Release, 1978 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Geological Survey, “Water Resources Investigations in Texas”, 1965 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Geological Survey Circular #725, “Geological Estimates of Undiscovered Recoverable Oil and Gas Resources in the United States”, circa 1974 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Golden Eagles, Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Service (HCRS), Brochures and Press Releases, 1969-1978 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Land Use Planning Bill, Correspondence and Resolution, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Matagorda Island Air Force Range, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - National Park Service (NPS), Correspondence, 1951-1977 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - National Park Service (NPS), Seasonal Employment Materials, 1963 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - National Park Service (NPS), Summer Employment, Application Materials, Bulletins, and Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - National Park Service (NPS), Summer Employment, Pamphlets, 1970-1978 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - National Urban Recreation Study, Executive Report, 1978 February (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Office of the Secretary, Correspondence and Reports, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - “Old Cattle Trails of the Southwest: A National Scenic Trail Study”, 1975 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Out-of-District Correspondence, 1976 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Out-of-District Correspondence, 1978 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Padre Island, Master Plan, 1973 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Park Proposal, Maps, 1967-1968 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Preservation of Historic Homes, Correspondence and Legislative Reports, 1966 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Press Releases and Reports, 1967 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1969 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1970 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1971 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1972 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1973 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases and Printed Materials, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Printed Materials, 1974 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Public Land Range Appraisal, Analysis, “Economic Relationship of Grazing Fees and Permitted Use of Public Rangelands to Net Income of Western Livestock Ranches”, circa 1962 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Public Land Range Appraisal, Brochure, “Development Program for the National Forests”, 1961 November (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Public Land Range Appraisal, Brochure, “Program for the Public Lands and Resources”, 1962 May (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Public Land Range Appraisal, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Public Land Range Appraisal, Report, “The Look Forward: A Trial Program of Public Land Range Appraisal”, 1962 June (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Report, Public Works for Water and Power Resources Development, 1968 June 14 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Reports, 1969 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Reports, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Reports, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - “Seventh Report of the Texas Mapping Advisory Committee”, 1969 February (Box 128, Folder 17)
  - Department of Justice, 1947-1979, undated; 8
    Subseries VIII consists of materials relating to the Department of Justice. The content addresses law enforcement matters within the United States including immigration and the naturalization of citizens. There are three agencies that feature prominently in the subseries: the Federal Bureau of Investigation, the Immigration and Naturalization Service, and the Law Enforcement Assistance Administration.
    Folders in the subseries are arranged alphabetically by agency or material type. The materials are in good condition.
    - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, Report, Immigration Pool Issuances, 1965 August 23 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Correspondence, 1947-1961 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Correspondence, 1964-1971 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Correspondence, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), J. Edgar Hoover, Articles and Remarks, 1961-1962 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Opinion Ballots, 1971 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), Report, 1967 August 10 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), Application Forms and Pamphlets, 1959-1962 (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), Correspondence, 1951-1971 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1976 January (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1976 February (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1976 August (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1976 October (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1976 November (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1977 November (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), List, Naturalized Citizens, 1978 May-November (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), Pamphlet and Printed Materials, 1950-1965 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Investigation of President Harry Truman, Correspondence, 1952 (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1978-1979 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), General Briefing, 1978 May (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Grant Awards (1 of 2), 1968-1978 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Grant Awards (2 of 2), 1968-1978 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Report, Participating Institutions, 1978 August (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Speech, Richard Wertz, 1978 May 17 (Box 130, Folder 16)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (LEAA), Temple Junior College, Application and Correspondence, 1972 (Box 130, Folder 17)
    - Mexican Prisoner Transfer Treaty, Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Department of Labor, 1949-1978, undated; 9
    Subseries IX contains materials relating to the Department of Labor. Several topics such as migrant labor, workers’ safety and wages, and women in the workforce are represented in the subseries. There is also a significant batch of folders that consist of materials from OSHA, the Occupational Safety and Health Administration created under the Richard Nixon Administration in 1971.
    The folders in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by agency or material type. The materials are in good condition.
    - Braceros, Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 130, Folder 19)
    - Braceros, Minutes and Reports, 1958 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    - Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS), Correspondence and Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 130, Folder 21)
    - Charles Blake Files, 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    - Charles Blake Files, 1977-1978 (Box 130, Folder 23)
    - College Assistance Migrant Problem, Correspondence and Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1952 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Fact Sheets, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Federal Employees Compensation Act, Basic Forms, 1975 August (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Federal Employees Compensation Act, Report, “Federal Injury Compensation”, 1977 September (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - “Federal Register”, “Immigration: Availability of, and Adverse Effect Upon, American Workers”, 1968 September (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - Leaflets, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Legal Documents, 1949-1956 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Manpower Administration, Clippings and Resolutions, 1971-1974, undated (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Manpower Administration, Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Manpower Administration, Reports, 1969-1976 (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 133, Folder 12)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), “Federal Register”, 1976 April 23 (Box 133, Folder 13)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Notebook, New Initiatives and Case Studies, 1976 (Box 133, Folder 14)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), “OSHA General Industry Standards”, 1977 November 11 (Box 133, Folder 15)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Packet, “Here Are Some of the Reasons Why OSHA Inspects Small Business”, circa 1974 (Box 133, Folder 16)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Pamphlets, 1976, undated (Box 133, Folder 17)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Press Releases, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 18)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Printed Materials and Reports, 1975-1978 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA), Report, “The Shift to Common Sense Priorities”, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Press Releases, 1968 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases, 1970 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Press Releases, 1971-1974 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Printed Materials and Resolutions, 1950-1956 (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions and Statements, 1959 (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Statements, 1974 (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Statements, 1977 (Box 134, Folder 11)
    - Texas Sheep and Goat Raisers Association, Resolution, 1958 June 14 (Box 134, Folder 12)
    - “The Reader’s Digest”, “The Scandal of Unemployment Compensation”, 1960 April (Box 134, Folder 13)
    - “This is HowEL12 Camps for Migratory Workers in Agriculture Are Operated”, 1957 (Box 134, Folder 14)
    - Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division, Correspondence and Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 134, Folder 15)
    - “Women & Work,” Newsletters, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 16)
    - Worker Adjustment Assistance, Report, 1978 (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - Department of State, 1946-1978, undated; 10
    Subseries X is comprised of materials relating to the Department of State. Three of the most prominent entities represented among the materials include the Agency for International Development, Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, and the U.S. Foreign Service. The materials cover a broad array of topics including foreign affairs, refugees (particularly Indochinese refugees during the Vietnam War), and passports. Correspondence containing personal information on passports has been deaccessioned.
    - “A Guide to Visas, Passports, and Consular Services”, circa 1970s (Box 134, Folder 18)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), Bulletin, Buffalo Gourd, 1975 January (Box 134, Folder 19)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1962-1974 (Box 134, Folder 20)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), Correspondence and Press Releases, 1975-1978 (Box 134, Folder 21)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, Statement, 1963 June 21 (Box 134, Folder 22)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID), Handbook II, Country Contracting, 1975-1976 (Box 134, Folder 23)
    - Agency for International Development (USAID) and Arms Control and Disarmament Agency (ACDA), Telephone Directory, 1974 February (Box 134, Folder 24)
    - Appalachian Regional Development Act (ARDA), Hearings, 1967 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - Board for International Food and Agricultural Development (BIFAD), Newsletters, 1978-1979 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, Manuals, 1970-1973 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, Newsletters, 1978 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, Report of the Visa Office, 1973 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, “1976 Report of the Visa Office”, 1977 December (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Clippings and Pamphlets, 1965 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1950 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1951 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 135, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 135, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1954 (Box 135, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 135, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 135, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1961 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Council for Inter-American Security, “A Survey of Hemispheric Issues”, 1977 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - “Foreign Affairs Memorandum”, 1978 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Service Research, Leaflet, circa 1960s (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Franscati Orphan’s Home, Correspondence, 1950 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Interagency Task Force for Indochina Refugees, “A Guide to Two Cultures”, 1975 August (Box 137, Folder 14)
    - Interagency Task Force for Indochina Refugees, Printed Materials, 1975, undated (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Interagency Task Force for Indochina Refugees, “Report to the Congress”, 1975 September (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Interagency Task Force for Indochina Refugees, “Vietnamese Refugee Orientation Handbook”, 1975 July (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - International Cooperation Administration (ICA), Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Memorandum, “Aids to Business (Overseas Investment)”, 1964 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Panama, Printed Materials, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Participant Training Program, Brochures, 1970, undated (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Passport Information, 1965-1975 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Passports, Leaflets, 1972-1977, undated (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 1966 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Secretary of State (SOS), Press Conference Speeches, 1977-1978 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Strategic Arms Limitations Talks (SALT), Reports, 1978 (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Foreign Service, Diplomat List, 1964 August (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Foreign Service, Directory, 1963 April (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Foreign Service, Directory, 1964 July (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Foreign Service, “1964 Examinations of Foreign Service Officers” (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Foreign Service, “1978 Examination for Foreign Service Officer Careers” (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Information Agency (USIA), Correspondence, 1960-1972 (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Vietnamese Orphans, Correspondence and Fact Sheets, 1975 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Department of Transportation, 1967-1978, undated; 11
    Subseries XI contains materials pertaining to the Department of Transportation which began operations in 1967. The content of the subseries relates to several agencies within the Department of Transportation including the Federal Aviation Administration, the Federal Highway Administration, and the U.S. Coast Guard which eventually transferred to the Department of Homeland Security in 2003. Additional materials concerning transportation, particularly those relating to AMTRAK, can be found in Series I. since the materials predate the establishment of the Department of Transportation.
    Folders in this subseries are arranged alphabetically by agency or material type. The materials are in good condition.
    - AMTRAK, Clippings, 1970-1972 (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Announcements, 1970-1977 (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Announcements, Clippings, and Press Releases, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 1)